[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Diamonds are Forever, Bond encounters a villain named Bambi.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aspen is beneficial to a horse that is nervous and anxious, shies at invisible objects in a familiar arena and bolts for no reason.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Back to the Future movie series, what was the family name of Michael J. Foxs character?", "correct_answer": "McFly", "incorrect_answers": ["McDoughal", "McAddams", "Macmillan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal character did Jada Pinkett Smith voice in the 2008 comedy movie Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa?", "correct_answer": "Hippopotamus", "incorrect_answers": ["Aye-aye", "Giraffe", "Penguin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which American author wrote the so called Rabbit novels - Rabbit, Run, Rabbit Redux, Rabbit Is Rich, Rabbit At Rest and Rabbit Remembered?", "correct_answer": "John Updike", "incorrect_answers": ["William Faulkner", "Michael Crichton", "Ken Kesey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which brand of paper is the The Quilted Quicker Picker-upper?", "correct_answer": "Bounty", "incorrect_answers": ["Sparkle", "Scotts", "Browny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about almonds?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The sweet almond contains no carbohydrates.", "They lower LDL cholesterol, the bad cholesterol.", "They are very rich in vitamin E."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2002 film was adapted from the third novel of The Vampire Chronicles series.", "correct_answer": "Queen of the Damned", "incorrect_answers": ["Interview with the Vampire", "The Vampire Lestat", "Underworld"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the bra first appear?", "correct_answer": "2000 BC", "incorrect_answers": ["4000 BC", "1000 BC", "3000 BC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ernest Borgnine portrayed Lt. Quinton McHale on The Phil Silvers Show from 1962-1966.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services (CMS) used to be known as what?", "correct_answer": "The Health Care Financing Administration (HCFA)", "incorrect_answers": ["Medicare", "The Centers for Disease Control (CDC)", "The Department of Health and Human Services (DHHS)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pax Romana,  the long period of relative peace experienced by states within the Roman Empire took place between these years.", "correct_answer": "27BC - 180", "incorrect_answers": ["33 - 180", "180 - 436", "145 - 254"]}]